theperspective.com 2019-03-23

# Privacy Policy | The Perspective

**Privacy Policy**

Last updated: May, 2018

Perspective Media Ltd. (the “Company”) respects your privacy. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains the privacy practices of Company in connection with the users (“you”, “your” or “user”) access or use of the following websites owned and operated by Company and included therein: [www.theperspective.com](http://www.theperspective.com/) (the “Website”).  and Company’s products, mobile apps, software, data feeds, and services offered to you on, from or through the Company websites (collectively the “Service”). The Privacy Policy describes the ways Company collects, processes and uses your Personal Information (as defined below) when using the Service and the rights and options available to you with respect to your information.

We may change or update this policy from time to time, and we will notify you of any changes by changing the “last updated” notice set forth above.

This policy is incorporated to the Service’s [Terms of Service](https://www.theperspective.com/terms-of-use/) (the “Terms of Service” or the “Terms”) and is a legally binding agreement between you and us.

BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE OR OUR SERVICES, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS REQUIRED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW WITHIN YOUR JURISDICTION.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [ **info@theperspective.com**](mailto:info@theperspective.com) (or as described below).

 **What type of information do we collect?**

We may collect two types of information from you.

The first type of information is non-identifiable information which may be made available via the use of the Site or Services. Thus, we are not aware of the identity of the user from which the Non-Personal Information was collected. (“ **Non-Personal Information** ”).

The Non-Personal Information collected by us may include your aggregated usage information and technical information transmitted by your device, including but not limited to: type of browser and the settings, operating system, type of the device used to access our Services, your ISP, log data, visits to the Website, pages viewed, Items views or Items saved, date and time stamp, duration on the page, approximate geographical location; (if you have that functionality set up) and the path taken in the Website.

The second type of information is individually identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort identify an individual (“ **Personal Information** ”). When you access or use the Website or Service we may collect the following Personal Information:  **(i) Contact details:**  If you voluntarily contact us whether through the “Contact Us” page in the Site, by sending us an email, or any other request or notification, you may be required to provide us with certain information such as your name and email address;  **(ii) Newsletter Subscription:**  If you voluntarily subscribe to our Newsletter you will be asked to provide us with your name and email address. You can unsubscribe at any moment through the “unsubscribe” link;  **(iii) User’s Comments:**  if you voluntarily leave a comment on the Website or submit a review you will be asked to provide us with your name and email address. If we will decide to post your comment, it will be posted under the name you have provided;  **(iv) Content Uploaded to Site.** Any personal information or picture content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in My Perspective feature, etc.) becomes publicly available and you acknowledge that third parties may access, collect and use such content.  **(v) Registration:**  In order to register and use the Services (such as The Perspective Challenge) we require basic contact information such as: username, photos, email and password. Alternatively, you register to the Service via your existing third party social network account accounts such as Facebook. In the event that you register to the Services through your existing social network account, then such social network account provides us with access to certain information about you as is stored therein (e.g. full name, e-mail and any additional information which you made public). Note During the registration process you will be provided with a user name and a password, which can be replaced following login in. You represent and warrant that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your username and password and that you will not provide inaccurate, misleading or false information to us. If information provided to us subsequently becomes inaccurate, not updated, misleading or false, you will promptly notify us of such change.

If we combine Personal Data with Non-Personal Data, the combined data will be treated as Personal Data for as long as it remains combined.

You may upload your personal information to the Service and share the information with Company and users of the Service. The personal details that you upload, including any materials, videos, sound recordings, compositions, pictures, song lyrics, text, software, scripts, graphics, photos, videos, audiovisual combinations, interactive features and other materials you may view on, access through, or contribute to the Service (“Content”), may be accessible to other users and may appear in search results on the Service. PLEASE USE CAUTION AND COMMON SENSE WHEN YOU UPLOAD YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, ESPECIALLY ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION.

The content that you upload to the Service is not private

You have the control over the Content that you wish to upload to the Service. The Content you submit to the Service will be associated with your account. However the Content that you upload may be available to other users of the Service and the Service’s personnel, as well as to users of the Internet in general, including through the use of search engine services.

 **What does Company do with your personally identifiable information?**

We collect Personal Information for the following purposes:

  * The legitimate interest of operating the service.
  * as well as recommend content based on your preferences.
  * To respond to users’ requests and feedbacks.
  * To allow you to register for the Services
  * To respond to claims that any content available through the Service violates rights of third-parties, to resolve disputes and enforce our policies, including investigation of potential violations thereof, for the purpose of law enforcement or in accordance with any applicable law or regulation.
  * To post your Content on the Service and to facilitate communication between you and the Service and other users;
  * To provide you with further marketing and advertising material, subject to your prior indication of consent on the Service. At any time, you may opt out of the Service’s mailing lists, by changing your preferences in your Service’s personal account.

 **We collect Non-Personal Information for the following purposes**

  * The legitimate interest of operating the service.
  * To perform research, analytics or for statistical purposes.
  * To detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.

 **Important notice about children’s privacy**

You represent and warrant that, (i) if you are located in the US, you are at least 13 years of age; or if you are located in any other GEO, you are above the age defined as “child” under applicable laws in your jurisdiction (collectively “ **Child** ” or “ **Children** ”); and (ii) you are of legal competence to enter into this Privacy Policy. If you are under 18, please be sure to read the terms of this Privacy Policy with your parents or legal guardians. If you become aware or have any reason to believe that a Child has shared any identifiable information with us, that you want removed, please contact us at: [ **info@**](mailto:info@) ** _theperspective.com_**

 **Provisions relevant to Non U.S. users**

We may store or process your information in the United States or in other countries. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (“ **EEA** “) we will take appropriate measures to ensure that your information receives an adequate level of data protection upon its transfer outside of the EEA. If you are a resident of a jurisdiction where transfer of your data requires your consent, then your consent to this Privacy Policy includes your express consent for such transfer of your Personal Information.

 **How does Company use aggregated information?**

Company may use anonymous, statistical or aggregated information collected on the Service, including posting, disseminating, transmitting or otherwise communicating or making available such information through the Service, or to users on the Service, to the Service’s suppliers, partners and any other third party, at the Service’s sole discretion.

Company may also use anonymous, statistical or aggregated information to properly operate the Service, to improve the quality of the Service, to enhance your experience, to create new services and features, including customized services, to change or cancel existing Content or service, for marketing and advertising purposes, and for further internal, commercial, and statistical purposes.

 **Sharing information with others**

We do not sell, trade, or rent users’ Personal Information to other parties. We may share information solely in the following events:

  * When you use the Service, or when you take part in any content-related activity. In these cases, the Service will share your information to the extent necessary to facilitate your use of the Service;
  * If Company reasonably believes that you have breached the Service’s Terms of Service, or abused your rights to use the Service, or performed any act or omission that Company reasonably believes to be violating any applicable law, rules, or regulations. Company may share your information in these cases, with law enforcement and other competent authorities and with any third party, as may be required to handle any result of your wrongdoing;
  * If Company is required, or reasonably believes that it is required by law and/or law enforcement agencies to share or disclose your information;
  * In any case of dispute, or legal proceeding of any kind between you and Company or between you and other users with respect to, or in relation with the Service;
  * To operate the Service and Company’s services, to send messages, and to provide search results and links;
  * In any case where Company reasonably believes that sharing information is necessary to prevent imminent physical damage or damage to property;
  * If Company organizes the operation of the Service within a different framework, or through another legal structure or entity, or if Company is acquired by, or merged into or with another entity, provided however, that those entities agree to be bound by the provisions of this policy, with respective changes taken into consideration;
  * Company may also share personally identifiable information with companies or organizations connected, or affiliated with Company, such as subsidiaries, sister-companies and parent companies, and other partners, with the express provision that their use of such information must comply with this policy.
  * We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of the Service. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users access the Service, what pages they visit when they do so, etc. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve our Service. Google Analytics collects certain identifiers assigned to you on the date you visit sites, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits by disabling cookies on your browser. To learn more how Google uses data from our use of Google Analytics Cookie we recommend you review Google’s policies located at: [ **www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners**](http://www.cheezburger.com/www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners). We also encourage you to review the Google Analytics’ currently available opt-outs for the web tool available at: [ **https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/**](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).
  * Identifiers – we may disclose or share identifiers collected by us (as detailed above), for the purpose of operating our business and providing the Services, as well as to calculate payments and detect fraud, security or technical issues in connection with the Service;

 **Choice**

 ** _Notifications opt out :_**

 ** _Chrome_**[ ** _https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/3220216?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop &hl=en_**](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/3220216?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en)

 ** _Mobile Opt-out:_**

Android-[ **https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922**](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922)  _or  _IOS-[ **https://support.apple.com/en-il/HT205223**](https://support.apple.com/en-il/HT205223).

 ** _Website Opt-out:_**

You may control how your browser responds to cookies by adjusting the privacy and security settings of your web browser.

Please refer to the support page of the browser you are using. In this regard, following are some links which you may find useful:

  * Google Chrome: [ **https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en**](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)
  * Firefox: [ **https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences**](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)
  * Internet Explorer: [ **https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies**](https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies)
  * Safari: [ **https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411**](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411)
  * Edge: [ **https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy**](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy)
  * Opera: [ **http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/**](http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/)

 ** _Industry Standards_**

You may opt out of certain advertisers’ cookies and browser-enabled, interest-based advertising at the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) website- [ **NAI consumer opt-out**](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/) and the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (“DAA”) website- [ **DAA opt-out page**](http://www.aboutads.info/). If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising, you may [ **click here**](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

 **opt-out**

You may also Contact Us at [info@theperspective.com](mailto:info@theperspective.com) and we will be happy to assist you. Note that once you opt out, part of the Services provided by us might no longer be available and some features may not work if you revoke the data transfer.

In the event, that you have any additional complaints about your privacy rights, please initially contact the Data Protection Officer. Please note that you have the right at any time to contact your local data protection authority.

 **User Rights**

You have a right to know what information we hold about you and, in some cases, to have such information communicated to you. You may also ask for our confirmation as to whether or not we process your Personal Information. You can also have any identifiable information (like your name, email or user created content) removed by writing to us at [info@theperspective.com](mailto:info@theperspective.com)

 **Data retention**

We retain the Non-Personal Information we collect for as long as needed to provide the Service, carry out our business purpose, perform our contract with you, and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements, in accordance and compliance with applicable laws, or until an individual request us to delete its Personal Information, as detailed above, but not longer than 26 months in an identifiable form, or as required by law.

Please note that unless you decide to delete your User Account by sending us a request do so, or any part thereof, or instruct us otherwise, we retain the information we collect for as long as needed to perform the above. Once you delete your Account you will not be able to recover it and will have to register again with a new account in case you choose to use the Service.

In addition, some of the data we receive depends on your privacy settings with the social network (i.e., Facebook) and you should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to our Site.

We are entitled to rectify, replenish or remove incomplete or inaccurate information, at any time and at our sole discretion.

 **Cookies**

Company may use cookies on the Service. Cookies are packets of information sent by the Service’s servers to your web browser and then sent back by the browser each time it accesses the Service’s servers. The cookies may contain a variety of information, such as the content of search queries, the Service’s pages you have accessed, session durations and IP addresses.

The Service may use cookies for various purposes, such as to save you the need to re-enter your user name and password each time you log-in on the Service, to facilitate the use of services on the Service, to collect statistical information with respect to the use of the Service, to verify information, to customize Service to your personal preferences and for information security purposes. Some of the cookies may expire when the session ends and you exit your browser. Other cookies are saved on your computer’s hard drive. If you wish to block the Service’s cookies, then please use the help button in your browser and follow the necessary instructions. However, bear in mind that disabling cookies may complicate or even prevent your use of the Service, or certain features thereof. You can find more information about cookies at [ **www.allaboutcookies.org**](http://www.cheezburger.com/www.allaboutcookies.org). You may remove our cookie by following the instructions of your device preferences; however, if you choose to disable our cookie, some features of our Service may not operate properly and your online experience may be limited. You may control how your browser responds to cookies by adjusting the privacy and security settings of your web browser.

 **Advertising Campaigns**

Company permits third party advertising companies to place advertisements on Company Services and manage their display. In order to manage the advertisements, these companies post cookies on your computer and embed web beacons in the advertisements or in Company Websites’ pages. Web beacons are tiny graphics with unique identifiers, embedded in web pages and used to assist in collecting information about the sites usage. The collected information may identify you, and is only intended to match the displayed advertisements to your personal interests. The use of cookies and web beacons by advertising companies is subject to their own privacy policies and not to this Privacy Policy. Such companies have no access to Company’s Websites’ cookies and Company has no access to their cookies. Should you wish to check the privacy policies of the companies that are managing the advertising scheme on Company Websites, you may do so via their own websites. To opt out of Google’s “interest-based ads” and to learn more about Google’s collection of your personal information to serve ads in connection with Company Websites, [ **click here**](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/). For FB [click here](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/). We may use Brightcom for targeted advertising, for more information please see Brightcom’s privacy policy available [ **here**](http://www.brightcom.com/privacy-policy/). We use Mindad media for media advertising. for more information please see Mindad’s privacy policy available  ** _[here](http://mindadmedia.com/gdpr/)_**

To receive further information about the advertising companies that Company works with, please contact us at:  ** _info@theperspective.com_**

 **Contact Company**

You may send Company requests, responses, questions and complaints, by contacting Company at [ **info@theperspective.como**](mailto:info@theperspective.como), or by post mail to:

Perspective Media Ltd.  
Reut 10, Apt 7, Hod Hasharon, Israel
